let theQueensGambitQuestions = [
	{
		question: "About how many households have watched the series in its entirety?", 
		choices = ["45 million", "57 million", "62 million", "80 million"],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
  {
		question: "Beth struggles to become a Grandmaster in chess..", 
		choices = ["from the age of 7 to 20", "from the age of 10 to 29", "from the age of 8 to 22", "from the age of 9 to 25"],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
  {
		question: "Though the show was set in the 1960s, when were women actually allowed to compete in the World Chess Championship?", 
		choices = ["1950s", "1970s", "1980s", "1970s"],
		correctAnswer:  2
	},
  {
		question: "The miniseries is based on the 1983 novel of the same name by...", 
		choices = ["Walter Tevis", "Katherine Neville", "Stefan Ziger", "Brad Pitt"],
		correctAnswer: 0
	},
  {
		question: "Which behavior do we see in Beth that is realistic of many chess players?", 
		choices =  ["Visualizing moves on the floor", "Visualizing moves on the ceiling", "Visualizing moves on her palm", "Visualizing moves on her dreams"],
		correctAnswer: 1
	},
  {
		question: "The Queen's Gambit is a(n)...", 
		choices = ["Canadian TV series by Netflix", "UK TV series by Netflix",  "American TV series by Netflix", "Spanish TV series by Netflix"],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
  {
		question: "Which chess champion may you recognize from also being an actor in five Harry Potter movies?", 
		choices = ["Harry Beltik",  "Vasily Borgov", "Benny Watts",  "Harry Potter"],
		correctAnswer: 1
	},
  {
		question: 'Complete the quote: \
â€œMen are gonna come along and wanna teach you things...', 
		choices = ["Kick them back as hard as you can", "Show them what you've got", "Doesn't make them any smarter", "Don't listen to them"],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
  {
		question: "Which player scares Beth most?", 
		choices =  ["The Chinese", "The Russian", "The German", "The Spanish"],
		correctAnswer:  1
	},
  {
		question: "What do chess experts think of the show overall?", 
		choices = ["They say it's unrealistic", "They say it's very believable",  "They say only a few parts of the show are accurate", "They say it's very bad"],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
];